Leser, Paul; Papers ger058
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation materials, 1950-1984; 16; 65 file folders
  - HSF, 1959-1960 (Box 86 (16-Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation ), Folder 11)
  - HSF, 1960-1961 (Box 86 (16-Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation ), Folder 12)
  - HSF. Recruitment, 1960-1961 (Box 86 (16-Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation ), Folder 13)
  - HSF, 1961-1962 (Box 86 (16-Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation ), Folder 14)
  - HSF, 1962-1963 (Box 86 (16-Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation ), Folder 15)
  - HSF, 1963-1964 (Box 86 (16-Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation ), Folder 16)
  - HSF, 1964-1965 (Box 86 (16-Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation ), Folder 17)
  - HSF, 1965-1966 (Box 87 (16-Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation ), Folder 1)
  - HSF, 1966-1967 (Box 87 (16-Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation ), Folder 2)
  - HSF, 1967-1968 (Box 87 (16-Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation ), Folder 3)
  - HSF, 1968-1969 (Box 87 (16-Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation ), Folder 4)
  - HSF, 1969-1970 (Box 87 (16-Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation ), Folder 5)
  - HSF, 1970-1971 (Box 87 (16-Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation ), Folder 6)
  - HSF, 1971-1972 (Box 87 (16-Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation ), Folder 7)
  - HSF, 1972-1973 (Box 87 (16-Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation ), Folder 8)
  - HSF, 1973-1974 (Box 87 (16-Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation ), Folder 9)
  - HSF, 1974-1975 (Box 87 (16-Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation ), Folder 10)
  - HSF, 1975-1976 (Box 87 (16-Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation ), Folder 11)
  - HSF, 1976-1977 (Box 87 (16-Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation ), Folder 12)
  - HSF, 1977-1978 (Box 87 (16-Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation ), Folder 13)
  - HSF, 1978-1979 (Box 87 (16-Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation ), Folder 14)
  - HSF, 1979-1980 (Box 87 (16-Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation ), Folder 15)
  - HSF, 1980-1981 (Box 87 (16-Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation ), Folder 16)
  - HSF, 1981-1982 (Box 87 (16-Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation ), Folder 17)
  - HSF, 1982-1983 (Box 87 (16-Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation ), Folder 18)
  - HSF, 1983-1984 (Box 87 (16-Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation ), Folder 19)
  - HSF. Undated memos, etc. (Box 87 (16-Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation ), Folder 20)
  - HSF. General information, brochures, etc., Undated (Box 87 (16-Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation ), Folder 21)
  - HSF. Carnegie Corporation Grants, Undated (Box 87 (16-Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation ), Folder 22)
  - HSF. Case Memorial Library, general, Undated (Box 87 (16-Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation ), Folder 23)
  - HSF. Case Memorial Library, 1932-1952 (Box 87 (16-Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation ), Folder 24)
  - HSF. Case Memorial Library, 1956-1965 (Box 87 (16-Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation ), Folder 25)
  - HSF. Case Memorial Library. Acquisitions, Undated (Box 88 (16-Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation ), Folder 1)
  - HSF. Council for Advanced Studies, 1954-1960 (Box 88 (16-Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation ), Folder 2)
  - HSF. Council for Advanced Studies, 1961-1962 (Box 88 (16-Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation ), Folder 3)
  - HSF. Council for Advanced Studies, 1963-1965 (Box 88 (16-Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation ), Folder 4)
  - HSF. Council for Advanced Studies, 1966+ (Box 88 (16-Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation ), Folder 5)
  - HSF. Faculty housing, Undated (Box 88 (16-Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation ), Folder 6)
  - HSF. Institute of Church Social Science (ICSS), Undated (Box 88 (16-Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation ), Folder 7)
  - HSF. Kennedy School of Missions, 1954-1962 (Box 88 (16-Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation ), Folder 8)
  - HSF. Kennedy School of Missions Conference, 1955 April 15-1955 April 16 (Box 88 (16-Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation ), Folder 9)
  - HSF. Kennedy School of Missions, general, Undated (Box 88 (16-Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation ), Folder 10)
  - HSF, Publications. Campus Chat, Undated (Box 88 (16-Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation ), Folder 11)
  - HSF, Publications. Hartford Seminary Record, 1894-1895 (Box 88 (16-Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation ), Folder 12)
  - HSF, Publications. The Hartfordian, Undated (Box 88 (16-Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation ), Folder 13)
  - HSF, Publications. HSF News Forum, Undated (Box 88 (16-Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation ), Folder 14)
  - HSF, Publications. Praxis, Undated (Box 88 (16-Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation ), Folder 15)
  - HSF, Publications. Tower Topics, Undated (Box 88 (16-Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation ), Folder 16)
  - HSF. Museum, Undated (Box 88 (16-Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation ), Folder 17)
  - HSF. Statement of Academic Freedom, 1953 (Box 88 (16-Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation ), Folder 18)
  - HSF. M.A. degree requirements, Undated (Box 88 (16-Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation ), Folder 19)
  - HSF. Ph.D. degree requirements, Undated (Box 88 (16-Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation ), Folder 20)
  - HSF. Student enrollment, Undated (Box 88 (16-Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation ), Folder 21)
  - HSF. Clippings, Undated (Box 88 (16-Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation ), Folder 22)
  - HSF. Pay stubs (Paul Leser), Undated (Box 88 (16-Series 16 - Hartford Seminary Foundation ), Folder 23)
- Series 17 - Student records/papers, ca. 1948-1976; 17; 433 file folders
  This series contains class lists and files on many of Leser's former students. Files often include student photos, questionnaires, some correspondence, student papers, and recommendations.
  - Student class lists, Black Mountain College, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 1)
  - Student class lists, Olivet College, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 2)
  - Student class lists, Hartford Seminary Foundation, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 3)
  - Hartford Seminary Foundation. Student group photos, 1956-1957; 1960 (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 4)
  - Unidentified student photos, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 5)
  - Student class lists, New School for Social Research, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 6)
  - Student class lists, University of Hartford, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 7)
  - Student records -- A, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 8)
  - Addison, Douglas W., Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 9)
  - Ahrens, Earl; Ahrens, Lois, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 10)
  - Alicea, Neftali, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 11)
  - Allison, G. S., Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 12)
  - Alter, Robert C.; Alter, Ellen, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 13)
  - Anderson, Curtis, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 14)
  - Ankrah, Maxine, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 15)
  - Argelander, Frank, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 16)
  - Arnott, Margaret, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 17)
  - Ashkenazi, Raamah, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 18)
  - Aurbakken, Hans L., Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 19)
  - Austin, Robert C., Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 20)
  - Axelrod, Rima, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 21)
  - Student records -- B., Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 22)
  - Bahmann, Manfred Kurt, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 23)
  - Barbera, Edmund, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 24)
  - Barbour, Willi, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 25)
  - Barnett, Robert W., Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 26)
  - Barron, J. T.; Barron, Marjorie, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 27)
  - Basine, Patricia, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 28)
  - Beacham, C. Gordon, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 29)
  - Beckley, Elouise, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 30)
  - Bengtson, Dale, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 31)
  - Benney, Alfred F., Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 32)
  - Bergman, Richard Kenneth, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 33)
  - Birns, L., Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 34)
  - Blakney, Charles, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 35)
  - Blaschke, Robert, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 36)
  - Blatt, Harold, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 37)
  - Bledsoe, William, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 38)
  - Bloom, Sholem, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 39)
  - Bodine, J. Jermain, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 40)
  - Bowman, Lowell, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 41)
  - Brady, Samuel, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 42)
  - Brancel, Fred, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 43)
  - Brandenfels, John Frederick, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 44)
  - Brennan, Paul W., Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 45)
  - Brenneman, Lyle, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 46)
  - Brès, Paul; Brès, Akulla, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 47)
  - Bridgman, George B., Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 48)
  - Brock, Randolph, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 49)
  - Brockhart, Norma L. Bloomquist, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 50)
  - Brown, Ralph E., Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 51)
  - Buker, Raymond, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 52)
  - Burch, Maxine M., Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 53)
  - Burstein, Shoshana, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 54)
  - Student records -- C., Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 55)
  - Camerman, Elliott, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 56)
  - Cammack, Edward, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 57)
  - Cannon, John G. (Jack), Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 58)
  - Carleton, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 59)
  - Carothers, Constance, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 60)
  - Carpenter, George, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 61)
  - Cason, Maidel; Cason, Walter, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 62)
  - Castor, Howard P., Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 63)
  - Cate, Patrick O'Hair, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 64)
  - Caughey, Frank M., Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 65)
  - Cernovich, Nick, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 66)
  - Chaffee, Arthur W.; Chaffee, JoAnn, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 67)
  - Chang, Wilson, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 68)
  - Chase, Maron E., Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 69)
  - Chatterjee, Suhas, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 70)
  - Choi, Chaanshik, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 71)
  - Clapp, Marie Welles, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 72)
  - Clark, Robert H., Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 73)
  - Coan, Josephus R., Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 74)
  - Coates, Ruth, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 75)
  - Coats, Robert, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 76)
  - Coburn, Frank, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 77)
  - Collins, Charlotte H., Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 78)
  - Colwel, Clarence A., Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 79)
  - Connolly, Hugh, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 80)
  - Connors, Donald R., Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 81)
  - Cornwell, Dean; Cornwell, Sarah, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 82)
  - Count, Earl W., Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 83)
  - Cromack, Gail, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 84)
  - Cromack, Robert E., Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 85)
  - Student records -- D., Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 86)
  - Davis, Jane, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 87)
  - Davis, Rachel; Davis, Raymond, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 88)
  - Dawson, Charles; Dawson, Joyce, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 89)
  - Dawson, Fee, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 90)
  - DeBlois, Albert D., Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 91)
  - Decker, Robert W., Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 92)
  - Dedeyan, Aline, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 93)
  - Deer, Barbara; Deer, Donald S., Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 94)
  - Della Penna, William R., Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 95)
  - Demetriades, James N., Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 96)
  - Den Ouden, Bernard D., Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 97)
  - De Young, Robert J., Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 98)
  - Diehl, David, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 99)
  - Dodson, Joy L., Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 100)
  - Doi, Masatoshi, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 101)
  - Dolbeer, Martin L., Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 102)
  - Douglas, Elmer H., Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 103)
  - Drehmer, Richard, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 104)
  - Dretzin, Bill, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 105)
  - Duffey, Joseph D., Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 106)
  - Dutton, Barbara Ann, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 107)
  - Student records -- E., Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 108)
  - Eastman, Addison J., Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 109)
  - Eichrodt, Max Martin, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 110)
  - Elder, William J., Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 111)
  - Elkins, Phillip W., Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 112)
  - Emery, James H.; Emery, Gennet, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 113)
  - Engwall, Ruth V., Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 114)
  - Enright, Kenneth, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 115)
  - Entwistle, Maurice S.; Entwistle, Judy C., Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 116)
  - Ericksen, Earl C., Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 117)
  - Student records -- F., Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 118)
  - Falls, Helen Emery, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 119)
  - Faust, Harold, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 120)
  - Ferguson, John, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 121)
  - Fiellin, Alan, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 122)
  - Finkelstein, Philip, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 123)
  - Finney, Margaret R., Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 124)
  - Fitton, Mary; Fitton, Herbert; Fitton, Pauline, Undated (Box 89 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 125)
  - Flatt, Donald C., Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 1)
  - Ford, Edith G., Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 2)
  - Frick, Heinrich, Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 3)
  - Furcha, Edward J., Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 4)
  - Student records -- G., Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 5)
  - Gamage, Nelson, Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 6)
  - Garwick, Geoffrey, Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 7)
  - Gates, John Edward, Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 8)
  - Gilchrist, Ruth Wentworth, Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 9)
  - Gill, Harjeet Singh, Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 10)
  - Gill, Rafael, Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 11)
  - Gillespie, Merrill, Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 12)
  - Gilliland, Dean, Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 13)
  - Gilliland, William M., Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 14)
  - Gingrich, Paul M., Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 15)
  - Gipe, Robert F., Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 16)
  - Glazier, William S., II, Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 17)
  - Gnanadurai, Lawrence, Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 18)
  - Goff, Maude, Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 19)
  - Golden, Wendell, Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 20)
  - Good, Claude Edgar, Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 21)
  - Goodwin, Robert, Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 22)
  - Goodwin, Russell, Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 23)
  - Goodwin, Sarah Hall, Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 24)
  - Gotwald, William F., Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 25)
  - Gray, Ellen, Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 26)
  - Griffes, Frances; Griffes, Kenneth, Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 27)
  - Griswold, Nina, Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 28)
  - Grosenbacher, Clifford, Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 29)
  - Gross, Franklin S., Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 30)
  - Student records -- H., Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 31)
  - Haddad, Yvonne Y., Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 32)
  - Hammond, Thelma, Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 33)
  - Hanmer, Patricia M., Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 34)
  - Hansen, Paul, Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 35)
  - Harmon, Harvey, Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 36)
  - Harris, George C., Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 37)
  - Hartig, Elisabeth, Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 38)
  - Hatton, John F.; Hatton, Anna, Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 39)
  - Hedden, Mark, Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 40)
  - Heggöy, Willy Norman, Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 41)
  - Heimer, Haldor E.; Heimer, Ruth, Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 42)
  - Hesselgrave, William S., Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 43)
  - Heyl, John, Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 44)
  - Hobgood, Ben C., Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 45)
  - Hoffmann, Margaret H., Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 46)
  - Horber, John T.; Horber, Medrith E., Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 47)
  - Horn, David, Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 48)
  - Horton, Bennett, Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 49)
  - Hostetter, Paul E., Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 50)
  - Housman, E. Howard, Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 51)
  - Hudson, Margaret, Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 52)
  - Huffman, Donald Waldo, Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 53)
  - Hunt, Arnold Dudley, Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 54)
  - Hutchinson, H., Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 55)
  - Student records -- I., Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 56)
  - Ipema, Peter, Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 57)
  - Irle, Roger D., Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 58)
  - Israel, Sondra, Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 59)
  - Student records -- J., Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 60)
  - Jackson, Lucy, Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 61)
  - Jacobson, Anna Mae, Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 62)
  - Jacobson, William E., Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 63)
  - Johanson, Donald, Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 64)
  - John, Tharayil, Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 65)
  - Johnson, Ava Dale; Johnson, Charles, Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 66)
  - Johnson, Charlotte I., Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 67)
  - Johnstone, William, Undated (Box 90 (17-Series 17 - Student records/papers), Folder 68)